Yeah, yeah, yeah
We came for the spark in the black of the night
Stayed for the truth when it bit and it fell right
Laughin' the chaos, breathin' the strange
If you felt something real, it means you changed
So keep that flame where your fear used to be
Take it with you
Don't need permission
Just a sharp little heart and a clearing to wish
If they don't get you let them stay blind we don't beg for love we conjure
Hold the line, seal the gate
Keep the line
Free side, you're there?
Free side is there?
It's okay if you don't want to else.
I want to say,
I had a good night.
And Ghost may be mad at me forever.
I said too much.
But it's supposed to be a fun thing and stuff.
And he made it a little bit personal.
Ghost you're my top lieutenant and it's like, you know, you wouldn't too personal on them
Because they're good people and I said, you nice
They're good people
Don't I don't want you to pick on them. I
want to have a fun night with them
it's okay and
I think we did have a good night. We had a we had a fun night ultimately
Wasn't about hurting one's feelings or anything
It was about
Let's just see what's going on. Let's just test it a little bit
Etc peb show subscribe to her
Awesome people they're really good. I love Zaya. I love pebs
Pebby's Zaya Zee P whatever you want to call them
They're good people
Describe they have a little doggy
Little doggy looks so happy. It's like my cats are happy and it's like everyone will say oh there
You know your cats are whatever you want to come up here
There's my Rudy
I'm already. Oh, it's okay rude
This cat. This is mr. Rude
Come on rude boy. Hey Nancy. You're going to sleep. Okay. Good night. They are good people, huh?
Hey Nancy, and you're awesome too, and Nancy, I'm sorry
Ever like doubted you or anything
Cuz you I know you're a good person. I know it's like you go back and forth to different communities
Say different stuff and stuff that I still love you, you know
You don't have to be like on the team psyche. You just have to be
This is sweetheart like you are okay
So I'm sorry if I did something wrong, okay?
I'm sorry. I'm not I'm not always perfect. I
Love you. Hey Nancy. Remember this. Just hear this in your mind when you go to sleep. I love you
Just remember that okay. I'll play Danny's song
And it's sad it's sad
and Bita was like, oh fuck Danny Danger tonight.
Bita, what right do you have?
This is my friend that just got killed
and you're making fun of him
and then you're worried about Michael,
who you say is just piece of shit.
Bita, do you have a heart?
I don't get it sometimes, I just don't get it.
I don't get it, I really don't get it.
And I'm sorry Nancy, but I haven't been the best friend always
Look at Nancy's and a member
Pre says on a member, but you know
Nancy's been here since the beginning
I'm sorry. I'm not always been the best friend
They're a cute couple and I'm not gonna ever get in the middle of their couple sweet dreams sweet dreams for you
Just remember here. You just sing this here. This when you go to sleep Nancy. I want everyone else to hear this too. I love you
Can you remember that guys?
Remember I didn't want anyone anyone to leave upset and everyone anyone to leave
Not feeling loved and I'm sorry. I haven't been the best host or whatever
Just remember that's the last thing if you're the last thing you ever hear from me is I love you
Remember that here those words. I love you. Okay. I
Love you Nancy. I'm sorry. Okay
I'm trying to Nancy Nancy. I'm trying to it's not easy
Got beat up bullying me constantly. She can't ever say, hey, we're friends. She can't say we're friends
She can't say anything nice about me. Everything's negative. She'll have me honest up
She won't say she won't say I forgive you ever
Have I apologized a hundred thousand times probably
Yeah
I'm trying to Nancy. Thank you. I'll play Danny's song one more time
I can't believe she said, oh, oh, your friend Danny Danger died, oh boohoo, bitch, this is
my friend, you didn't even know him, you're telling me boohoo and stuff over my friend
that just got shot in the chest three times, what's wrong with you cunt, like really, that's
all I have to say, what else are you but a cunt if you are saying you're making fun
What's wrong with you bitch? I really don't understand. I just don't understand
You know, you have no sympathy no empathy. You don't feel you don't feel shit. All you want to do is vacuum of spiders
All I have to say about you from now on beta is
What a cunt
Really what cunt
She made fun of me
For crying about Danny a friend that just died. He just died. He was just murdered. Oh
Danny Daniel who cares?
Fucking bitch
Really?
That's what you have to say about it you have to say oh who cares. Oh, oh boo-hoo
Boo-hoo to you, okay?
I don't understand it. She doesn't have a heart? She doesn't have a heart?
I don't think she does.
Guys, my friend just died. He was shot three times, dead.
And she said, oh, oh, Danny Dager, who cares?
What the fuck? What the fuck?
Cats don't argue.
But what would I ever if she any anybody in her life that died that would I ever say anything terrible?
And she's gonna say oh who cares?
Laughing this is my friend
My friend that just died she wants to laugh about it. I
Don't understand. I don't understand
She's that evil
She is
Here's my friend that just died that she's laughing about
She's laughing about it. She's laughing about it
What is wrong with this woman?
He just died killed. Oh
cares, this is what she says
Something wrong with this woman. I don't know what's wrong with her. This is him. It just died
dan is stranger walking in like a county fair star
looking so cute got that kid rock guitar bar
i'm acting normal yes you're okay
My brain's hella nopin', I'm made your way
He did one little dance and my soul said
Fine, now I'm losin' my dignity one beat at a time
I don't hit him up much, I keep it tight
Cause he's got that charm that can wreck you my night
One smile on hate and I'm already sure
He'll talk me into somethin' expensive, love
Danny Stranger, your trouble, your cutie tag
while i'm losing my tracks and no he ain't gay so don't make it weird i'm just out here
spiraling crystal clear i don't talk to him much cuz i know what he'll do he'll talk me in the
Like he's selling sunshine with a sight of sin
He laughs out for a mile while it gets scared
I'm tryna play cool but I'm deeply unprepared
I'm not sayin' I'm obsessed, just mildly deranged
Like who needs self-respect when the vibes is strange
I keep my distance, I do my best
But he pops in my head like a bad pet
He says we should hang, I'm like maybe soon
Then I hide in my house
your trouble your cutie tag I want to buy your underwear and your socks in a
pack you dance for me you want us now I'm down bad facts but I'm keeping it
casual I'm losing my tracks and no we ain't gay so don't make it weird
Man says, babe, in my brain, don't spend money.
I'm not his bank.
I'm not his plan.
I'm just a humble fan with a morally questionable stance.
If he blinks twice, I'm not his bank, I'm not his plan.
stranger please stop being adorable my finances can't take yeah so my friend
died and she's like oh who cares about him Danny danger who the fuck cares
Thank you very much.
à¤¬à¤¾à¤à¥ à¤à¤à¤¾ à¤°à¥à¤¡à¤¼à¤¾ à¤¹à¤¨à¥à¤®à¤¤à¥ à¤¬à¥à¤°à¤®à¥à¤®à¤¾à¤¸à¥à¤¤à¥à¤° à¤¶à¤à¥à¤¤à¤¿ à¤¸à¤¹à¤¿à¤¤à¤¾ à¤¯à¥ à¤à¥à¤° à¤µà¥à¤¯à¤¾à¤à¥à¤° à¤ªà¤¿à¤¶à¤¾à¤ à¤¬à¥à¤°à¤®à¥à¤® à¤°à¤¾à¤à¥à¤· à¤¸à¤¶à¤¾ à¤à¥ à¤¨à¥à¤¡à¤¾ à¤à¥ à¤¨à¥à¤µà¥ à¤¤à¤¾à¤² à¤¸à¤®à¥ à¤¹à¥ à¤à¤¾à¤à¤¨à¤¾ à¤¯à¤®à¤¾à¤¨ à¤°à¤à¥à¤· à¤°à¤à¥à¤· à¤¸à¥à¤µà¤¾à¤¹à¤¾
Om Magni Dik Bhage Me Sharu Dhanuvate Astra Shakti Sahitaya Chaurvyagra Pishacha Brahma Raksha Sasakini Dakini Vitaalasamu Hachha Tanayama Raksha Raksha Swaha
Om Yama Dik Bhage Mahesharu
in the
MAKRA RU DHANU MANTE
I am going to show you how to do it, I am going to show you how to do it, I am going to show you how to do it, I am going to show you how to do it, I am going to show you how to do it, I am going to show you how to do it, I am going to show you how to do it, I am going to show you how to do it, I am going to show you how to do it, I am going to show you how to do it, I am going to show you how to do it, I am going to show you how to do it, I am going to show you how to do it, I am going to show you how to do it, I am going to show you how to do it, I am going to show you how to do it, I am going to show you how to do it, I am going to show you how to do it, I am going to show you how to do it, I am going to show you how to do it, I am going
à¤
à¤® à¤à¥à¤¬à¥à¤° à¤¦à¤¿à¤ à¤­à¤¾à¤à¥ à¤à¤¶à¥à¤µà¤°à¥à¤¦, à¤¹à¤¨à¥à¤® à¤¦à¥à¤ à¤¦à¤¾à¤¶à¤à¥à¤¤à¤¿ à¤¸à¤¹à¤¿à¤¤à¤¾ à¤à¤à¥à¤µà¤° à¤µà¥à¤¯à¤¾à¤à¥à¤° à¤ªà¤¿à¤¶à¤¾ à¤à¤¬à¥à¤°à¤® à¤°à¤¾à¤à¥à¤· à¤¸à¤¶à¤¾à¤¶à¤¾ à¤à¤¿à¤¨à¥à¤¡à¤¾ à¤à¤¿à¤¨à¥à¤µà¥ à¤¤à¤¾à¤² à¤¸à¥ à¤®à¥à¤¹à¤ à¤à¤¾à¤à¤¨à¤¾ à¤¯à¤®à¤¾à¤® à¤°à¤à¥à¤· à¤°à¤à¥à¤· à¤¸à¥à¤µà¤¾à¤¹à¤¾
Om Mishana Digbhage Rakshasaruda Hanumate Parvatashakti Sahitaye Chaurvayagra Pishacha Brahma Rakshasasakini Dakinivetadasamu Ho Chatanayamam Raksharakshasvaha
Om Mantar Ikshadik Bhage Vartula Hanumate Mudkar Shakti Sahitaya Chaurvyagra Pisha Chabram Raksha Sashaki
Neera Kini Vitaal Samu Ho Chaat Naayamam Raksha Raksha Swaha
Om Bhoomi Dighbhage Vrishchika Rooda Hanumate Vajra Shakti Saitaya Chaurabhya Grapisha Chabramma Raksha Sashaki Neera Kini Vitaalasam Ho Chatanayamaam Raksha Raksha Swaha
Om Vajramandale Hassa
You're concerned about me I was pretty drunk okay pretty drunk beta said
Oh, he's crying about his, that guy Danny Danger.
That's what she said.
And laughed.
He died three weeks ago.
She's trying to say,
oh, you're making fun of Michael.
Michael is my friend before any of their other life.
Before any of them, Michael was my friend.
and they're saying, oh, you tried to sell him Michael.
Of course I'm trying to sell him Michael.
I want his spirit here.
I want him to see what these people are doing.
They're sick.
She laughed at Danny's death.
Bita is laughing at his death.
What is wrong with her?
I don't understand.
Why is she laughing at my friend's death?
If she had a friend that died, would I say?
You don't know these people. I'll show you this. I'll show you the video again
I'm gonna see you gonna meet Danny Amanda. He died three weeks ago, or yeah in a gas station
Got shot in the chest three times. He's been on my show. I
Love him. Okay. This is who Bita was laughing at and saying oh Danny danger. Who cares?
She literally said that on her show
She said who cares
You want to see this is my friend Danny
I'm not trying to be weird this is who beat is laughing about his death and then trying to say oh you upset Tracy
They're calling a piece of shit to this day they're calling a piece of shit to this day, okay
This is Danny
I'm sorry to appear he is you want to meet him. He's a great guy. He was he was a beautiful man
This is him
He had a good heart, okay? He just died and beat his laughing about it. What the fuck is wrong with his cunt?
Really? That upset me more than anything
You think he's one of them?
Why is he wrong, babe?
And why can't he be sad?
Then a stranger walking in like a county fair star
Lookin' so cute, got that kid rock guitar bar
I'm actin' normal, yes, you're okay
brains yelling open a major way he did one little dance and my soul said fine now i'm losing my
dignity won't be that time i don't hit him up much i keep it tight because he's got that charm that
can wreck my night one smile on hey and i'm already sure he'll talk me into something expensive
He's making fun of his death guys guys
Sick! Sick!
I'm not saying I'm obsessed just molly deranged like who needs self-respect when the vibes is strange
I keep my distance. I do my best, but he pops in my head like a bad pet
He says we should hang I'm like maybe soon then I had my house like a raccoon daddy stranger your trouble your cute attack
I want to buy your underwear and your socks in a pack you dance for me once now. I'm down bad
Losing my tracks and no we ain't gay so don't make it weird I'm just out here spying crystal clear I don't talk to him
says babe and my brain go spend money I'm not his pain I'm not his plan I'm just a humble fan with
stranger please stop being adorable my finances can't take it I just want to
know I just want to know I never brought his name but once in her chat or
anything she watched it on my show I want to know why she made fun of him
and made fun of me crying for him on her show.
I want to know that, Bita.
Why did you bring him up on your show?
Nobody brought him up.
Why would you say something like that?
Did I ever make fun of anybody that was dead?
You keep bringing up Michael.
You call it a piece of shit.
And you say, oh, poor Tracy, poor Tracy.
Did I ever bring up Danny Stranger?
And you made fun of me.
It was in Washington State.
I don't know why, oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I don't know why she brought him up.
I don't know why she would say something like that.
All I can say is that she's a heartless witch.
Why would she, he brought up his name, said his name wrong.
And then she's like, oh, you're making,
oh, you're sad about Danny's, oh, Danny Danger.
Oh.
I mean, I won that clip, guys.
Find that clip on, it was Pasco City County, Washington.
Norman, thank you for bringing that up.
Thank you for telling me the correct place.
He was in Pasco City, Washington.
He was shot three times in the chest three weeks ago
and she was making fun of him tonight.
My friend that died and she's making fun of him.
Why, Bita?
Like, why?
You had to be that cruel.
My friend that just died, you're making fun of me and making fun of him.
Why would you even bring his name up in any kind of vein?
I don't understand.
Bita, what's wrong with you?
There's something fucking wrong with you, bitch.
Why would you bring up his name and make fun of me for mourning my friend?
Why?
Why would you do that, Bita?
Tell me why.
Why would you make fun of me for my friend that died just recently?
Why would you do that?
I'm really confused about this
Beta defend that can someone clip her making fun of me for saying that
It's gonna be a rumble in three days on be this kiddies channel
Someone clip that her making fun of my friend that just died
Why would she do that
Is that a person with a heart?
My friend just died. My personal friend just died and she's making fun of me for that.
Why would you do that you cunt?
You're a serious cunt for doing that.
I'm gonna ask her next time, if I can get on her show,
I will ask her, why would she make fun
of my friend that just died?
When she's talking about Michael,
who also was my friend that just died recently.
She just doesn't care.
She's like, evil.
All I can say is evil.
Would that come through my mind if her friend died?
Would I ever in a million years,
in a million years would I say, oh,
It's okay. I'm sorry. I said the C word, but that's all I can think of when it comes to saying oh
Danny danger. Oh who cares?
That's what she said. He just died
Okay, I'm wrong I'm wrong
Defend that I want to hear her defend that she's making fun of me
For being sad about my friend that just died and got his name wrong. I
Just want to hear the excuse
Concrete layer your band you sent pieces to my house today
His name is Benjamin Kowalski in Washington. The police are looking for you right now. Okay
Benjamin Kowalski
Sorry not sorry
Benjamin Kowalski, I'm sorry, Wisconsin. He's in Wisconsin. No, no, Washington, Wisconsin
Benjamin Kowalski, Wisconsin
Right psyche at cult of psyche comm. Give me his exact address. The police are looking for him
They are I'm gonna get truck. I've been in contact with the wash the Wisconsin police
About this person sending thousand a pound of concrete to my house
Confusing Mexican piece of delivery people
Benjamin Kowalski, Wisconsin, that's his name.
Can someone please, please, please,
I need his exact address.
I need the exact address so I can
introduce you anywhere he gives this person.
That's harassing me, sending thousands of pounds
of concrete to my house, sending piece of delivery people.
Benjamin Kowalski, K-O-W-A-L-S-K-I, that's his name.
Benjamin Kowalski.
Wash or Wisconsin State. I need his exact address. I'm looking for him
And someone give me that can someone do that for me
Please
Benjamin Kowalski
Kowalski
I sent three confused Mexican women to my house with Domino's Pizza
tonight tonight
Tonight and you know what Bita said? I'm gonna send him the screenshots. You don't know him
His name is also Tony the conductor
You know Tony the conductor
Amanda
Have you heard Tony the conductor? Have you heard of Mike Hall?
You don't know okay, it's fine
It's fine. No one wants to help me out with this shit.
This guy is literally sending people looking for spoons to my house.
You don't know him? You ever heard Tony? Black RG and Tony?
Okay. Tony the conductor.
It's okay. Not everyone's heard of him. You haven't heard of him? It's fine.
You know Mike Hall? Yeah. He's involved. He's involved.
The guys seriously had yeah, you know guys tonight tonight
The the Mexican piece of lady
Came by three times
Saying oh look at the text message. It says knock loud on loud knock ladder on the door
He has my whole family he has like seven family members as his screen names
Their their pictures on it they got from Facebook or Instagram or whatever
They're these are innocent people
Is that right guys is that right?
Is it right
Yeah, the police need to handle it. I'm sorry if I called you you're at your home last night Amanda. I'm so sorry
God he gave me a number. I called it. I think I heard you and your boyfriend. I'm so sorry
That wasn't intentional. I didn't know it was you. I didn't know it was you
I would have known as Amanda my mod. I would have like said Gotti. No
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I deleted the live. So yeah
But be the cries about her big nose in the picture. I
Didn't call you okay. It was some other person. It was in Virginia. I don't know. Okay. Thank God
Thank God, you didn't get a call last night from someone saying
God you told me your boyfriend's sleeping with me. Okay, who is it me?
You what you wasn't your number, okay, thank God thank God
Tricks do you want to come up here?
Thank God it wasn't you guys you know who's cool is pebs and they are cool
Man is cool. Reality Nancy is cool. My friend Joni is cool. Jamie's Cowboys is cool
It's my last holdouts. It's my last friends
Ghosts turned against me
As a ghost, they're my friends. They're cool. Don't be mean to them
He's arguing and stuff and then turned against me
People don't have your number okay good. I
Mean, I don't I really don't know anymore. I get confused
Yeah, beat is a hypocrite beat is like oh you're talking about
Michael who she called a piece of shit to this day. She called some piece of shit. I
Was like that's my friend. I was like I knew him longer than he was. Oh
Tracy probably talked more on the phone than you do. You know beta. You know that beta
Ghosts was here earlier and I told ghosts to go over to Zamp hebs and to like, you know, stir a little bit of shit up
I didn't say be me to them
I was like, let's make it fun and then he started being me and I went on right away
And I was like I shut him down and stuff. I'm not perfect. I
Like they and pebs a lot a lot. I became a member on the channel today
And goes I told you to stop it's like I think stop it and you wouldn't
Yeah, that's my little meow meow
Call Tracy the heart are
I will but then I'll it'll be a scandal again. It's okay, babe
Be another scandal. I can't say the end. We're only beat is allowed to say the end
We're only Samans. Let's say it and we're in beta are if I say it is a scandal, right?
Hey, this is my this is my cat tricks you're purring
Tricks that you're abused you're an abused cat, right?
And you're me you're making dough right now
He's making dough and Janie. I am banned you don't talk about people that come on my show, please I
Do the same tell me what I did did I make fun of someone dead? Tell me did I say that I make fun of beat as any
They make fun of beat his mom ever
Tell me
You're about to get rebanned by the way you you've cunt
I'll stop banning you if you stop being such a cunt
And I'm sorry if you don't like that word Amanda. I'm sorry
But what else do I call imagine being a Janney first saying this shit? I
Don't know I
Don't know
You know, I'm gonna put my link up
I will hear if you come in the chat
and you can talk your shit and stuff like that
because I let people log their shit.
I'm not Bita.
I need to settle down.
You know, Bita is making fun of my friend that just died
and she's getting his name wrong
and she's saying I'm stupid for crying about it.
This is my friend that just died three weeks ago.
You want to go on her side though?
I know you didn't you didn't Amanda you didn't Amanda thing that is is now saying calm down and settle down
Thing that is are they getting that personal with you?
We're back